We're cascading down from the big target down to the daily target.
Once I click on this, I can see what my monthly missions
are inside of this certain category if I created these from, myself.
Or I added these things specific to from the quarterly targets. So
again, as it says, quarterly can seed the empty slots, or I
can edit my answers.
So I edited these specifically to make my own monthly missions. But
as I go through this, I can just click on these things.
And as I check off these boxes, I'm just being honest with
myself. About the things I have or have not done, and I
can break it down on a weekly basis, or I can add
new missions.
I can simply come in here and change the things that I
want to change specifically around whatever I'd like to do.
And we can go from there. Now, as I go back here,
now we're moving to what weekly. Okay. So weekly, it's going to
allow us to track our points on a weekly basis.